Javascript is required to run the page.

Privacy Policy
--------------

Image Chest and its affiliates (“IC” or “we”) are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell or distribute your personal information to third parties not affiliated with IC without your consent. This privacy policy explains the guidelines we use in protecting your privacy, which is applicable to the use of imgchest.com and our mobile applications.

#### Collection of Information

IC collects and temporarily stores information about your visit to our website through the use of cookies. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. We may employ cookie technology to help you move faster through our website, estimate our total audience size and traffic, or to help us improve our website’s experience by measuring which site areas are of greatest interest to users.

You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer, but you should note that if you do so, this may materially affect the functionality of our website and the information you can access through it. If you wish to find out more about cookies, or how to refuse cookies, please visit the Interactive Advertising Bureau’s website at www.allaboutcookies.org. Since we employ Google Analytics, Google AdWords Conversion tracker, and other Google services you may opt out of Google tracking specifically by visiting [this page](https://adssettings.google.com/).

IC collects information you provide directly to us through our website. As a visitor to our website, or as one who has otherwise requested information about Image Chest, you may choose to provide us with your name, email address, and other contact information (such as your telephone number). We will use the information you provide us for the purpose of responding to your request. The automatic anonymous data we collect is not linked to any personal information you provide.

IC collects usage statistics and crash reports through our mobile applications. The usage statistics and crash reports help us diagnose problems, help us understand how users interact with our mobile applications, and help us improve the performance of our mobile applications.

Any requests for data deletion can be sent through our [contact form](https://imgchest.com/contact).

#### Third Party Applications

IC uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help enhance and understand the use of our website and mobile applications. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. These services may use cookies and collect other information sent by your browser or mobile device, such as your IP address or the applications that were running at the time of a malfunction. This information is processed by these third party tools to generate statistical usage information. The collection of this information will allow us to better understand and improve the performance, usability, and effectiveness of our website and mobile applications.

#### Disclosure of Information

IC may disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

#### Users Access and Choice

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails.

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Links to 3rd Party Websites

The IC site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Image Chest. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

#### Notification of Changes

If we change our privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [contact us](https://imgchest.com/contact).  
Our mailing address is:

Image Chest  
PO Box 654  
Blacklick, Ohio 43004

#### About Image Chest

Image Chest makes sharing media easy. It can be used to share pictures and videos with friends, as well as share them on forums, blogs, social media, and more. Image Chest is where media finds it's uncensored and uncompressed forever home.

#### Links

Copyright © 2024 [Image Chest](https://imgchest.com/). All rights reserved.
